Guide to the Commons, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Commons, Yale University, records
1883-1927
RU 171
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.25
The records consist of financial files documenting the Commons, a Yale dining hall.
Yale University Dining Halls
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 5-F (YRG 5-F), Records documenting operations and administrative services at Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of financial files documenting the Commons, a Yale dining hall.
Universities and colleges -- Food service; Yale University -- Finance; Yale University Dining Halls
- Commons financial files, 1883-1927; Accession 1936-A-005
  - Payroll, 1883, 1884 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Payroll, 1899 October-1900 June (Box 1, Folder 2 - 10)
  - Daily Provisions Book, 1916 March-1918 September (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cash Receipts Ledger, 1919 September-1920 June (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Charge Ledger, 1919 September-1920 June (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Provisions & Supplies Ledger, 1919 September-1920 June (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Stock Book, 1919-1920 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence related to closing of Dining Hall, 1920-1921 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Inventories at closing, 1920-1921 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - The Kellogg Service, Inc. (1922-23)
    - Contracts with Yale, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence with Treasurer's Office, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Financial Records & Inventories, 1922 June-1922 December (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Financial Records & Biweekly Reports, 1922 September-1922 December (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Financial Records, 1923 January-1923 June (Box 3, Folder 22 - 23)
    - Repair & Replacement Bills, 1922-1923 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous & Unclassified, 1923? (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Accounts Payable, 1925 September-1927 June (Box 3, Folder 26 - 27)
  - Payroll, 1925 September-1926 December (Box 3, Folder 28 - 32)
  - Payroll, 1927 January-1927 June (Box 4, Folder 33 - 34)
  - Petty Cash Expenditures, 1925 October-1927 June (Box 4, Folder 35 - 36)
  - Resumes, 1926 September-1927 January (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Supplies Inventories, 1925 October-1926 June (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Supplies Inventories, 1926 October-1927 June (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous & Unclassified, 1925-1927 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Yale Theater Lunch Room
    - Accounts Payable, 1926 October-1927 May (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Payroll, 1926 October-1927 February (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Payroll, 1926 March-1927 June (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Resumes & Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 4, Folder 44)